The paper makes three contributions.
First,
it formulates the down-scaling operation directly
in the discrete domain as ideal downsampling,
properly accounting for anti-aliasing.
Second, it proposes a whole family of deep nets
that are truly scale-equivariant,
by rethinking every component, convolution layers,
non-linearities, and pooling,
and re-expressing them as Fourier layers that obey
a simple frequency-dependency rule.
Third, through extensive experiments on MNIST-scale
and STL-10,
it shows the model attains an absolute zero
end-to-end scale-equivariance error while
remaining competitive in classification accuracy
and more data-efficient in low-resource
settings.